https://www.trios.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Take our quiz and discover your dream job!
Icon-Quiz-Small
Created with Sketch.
Quiz
Have questions? Let’s chat, now!
Icon-Chat-Small
Created with Sketch.
Chat
Ready to begin your journey? Let’s get started!
Icon-Apply-Small
Created with Sketch.
Apply
Icon-Arrow-Button
Created with Sketch.
Top
Close Application Form
Fill in the form below and we will contact you as soon as possible.
First Name (Required)
First Name is required
Last Name (Required)
First Name is required
Email (Required)
Valid email address is required
Phone Number (Required)
Valid phone number is required
Postal Code
Please enter a valid postal code
What is Your Question?
Campus of Interest (Required)
Select a LocationBramptonHamiltonKitchenerLondonMississaugaScarboroughTorontoWindsor
Campus of Interest is required
Program of Interest (Required)
Select a ProgramAccounting & Payroll AdministratorAccounting & Payroll SpecialistAccounting ApplicationsAddiction WorkerAdministrative AssistantAdvanced Business Office ApplicationsApplications DeveloperBusiness AdministrationCommunity Services WorkerCompTIA A+ Certificate CourseCompTIA Network+ Certificate CourseDigital Marketing SpecialistEnterprise Web & Mobile DeveloperEquine Massage TherapyHonours Business AdministrationInformation Technology AdministratorInformation Technology ProfessionalInsuranceInsurance SpecialistLaw ClerkLaw and Security OfficerLegal AssistantMassage TherapyMedical Office AssistantMedical TranscriptionistNetwork AdministratorNetwork Support TechnicianOccupational Therapy AssistantOffice AdministratorPC Support TechnicianParalegalPersonal Support WorkerPharmacy AssistantPhysiotherapy AssistantPhysiotherapy Assistant/Occupational Therapy AssistantPolice FoundationsSupply Chain & LogisticsSupply Chain ManagementVideo Game ArtVideo Game DevelopmentWeb Technology Specialist
Program of Interest is required
How Did You Hear About Us?
Select an OptionN.A.EventNews or PrintOnlineOutreachRadioReferred by AgentReferred by Another SchoolReferred by OtherReferred by Student/AlumniSignTV
I consent to receive messages from triOS College - Business, Technology, Healthcare and have read & understand the terms provided. Mobile number will be used for triOS Alerts. Standard Msg & Data rates may apply. Text STOP to opt out or Help for help. Msg frequency varies. Privacy Policy. (Required)
Consent is required
Apply Now!
Home
Privacy Policy
Our Website Privacy Statement
In this policy, "we,'' "our" and "us" mean, as applicable, any of triOS Companies (namely triOS Corporation and triOS College Business Technology Healthcare Inc.) or the collective group
of companies, and "you" and "your" mean an individual who has made an application to us, or
has provided
When you enter into a purchase arrangement, or provide a guarantee in respect of, any of our products or services, and while you are our customer, you agree that:
1. We may collect and use personal information from you and about you for the following purposes:
– To understand your needs;
– To analyze the suitability of our products and services for you;
– To determine your eligibility for our products and services;
– To set up, manage and offer products and services that meet your needs;
– To provide you with ongoing service;
– To meet our legal and regulatory requirements;
– To investigate and administer funding sources available to you.
2. We may collect, use and disclose your Social Insurance Number for purposes relating to administering funding sources available to you on your behalf (i.e. OSAP, Human Resources Development Canada).
3. We may share information (except health information) about you to other companies within the triOS group of companies so that they may tell you about their products and services. There are some examples where triOS will not seek your consent for disclosure to outside third parties. These examples are:
– Where there is a legal obligation to disclose under a court or government order as for instance to detect or prevent illegal activity;
– Where personal information is given to their agents and service providers for services such as data processing of electronic fund transfers or loan collection;
– Where the disclosure is of regulated public information.
4. We may keep information about you in our records for as long is needed for the purposes described above, or as required by relevant regulatory requirements, even if you cease to be a customer.
5. All information which you give us at any time will be true and complete and you will not withhold any material information. You have the right to access, verify and update any personal information we have in your file.
6. We may use references you provide, to verify information, you give us and you authorize any person whom we contact in this regard to provide such information to us.
7. If any personal information changes or becomes inaccurate or out of date, you will tell us so we can revise our records.
8. You may now communicate with us directly through text messages. Simply fill out the form or text JOIN to 87467 to start receiving updates. Text/SMS Message-specific terms include:
– Standard message and data rates may apply;
– Message frequency depends on interaction level;
– Text HELP for more information, or STOP to cancel.
Refusing or Withdrawing Consent
Subject to legal and contractual requirements, you can refuse to consent to our collection, use or disclosure of information about you, or you may withdraw your consent to our further collection, use or disclosure of information at any time in the future by giving us reasonable notice, provided the consent does not relate to certain information required for credit or financing arrangements which you apply for or accept. If you refuse or withdraw your consent, we may not be able to provide you or continue to provide you with some products, services or information which may be of value to you.
You can tell us any time to stop using information about you to market our products and services or to stop sharing information with other companies in the triOS group of Companies.
If you wish to refuse consent or to withdraw consent as outlined within this policy, you may do so at any time by contacting the office of triOS with whom you deal with.
If You Apply for, Accept or Guarantee any For of Credit Facility With Us:
When you apply for, or accept, or guarantee a loan or credit facility and during the course of the loan or credit facility, we may use, give to, obtain, verify, share and exchange credit and other information (except health information) about you with others including credit bureaus, collection agencies, and other persons with whom you may have financial dealings, as well as any other person as may be permitted or required by law. You authorize any person whom we may contact in this regard to provide such information to us.
During the term of the loan or credit facility, you may not withdraw consent to our ongoing collection, use or disclosure of your personal information in connection with the loan or other credit arrangement you have with us or have guaranteed. We can continue to disclose such to credit bureaus even after your loan or credit facility has been retired, and you may not withdraw your consent to our doing so. We do this to help maintain the accuracy, completeness and integrity of the credit reporting system.
We may ask for your Social Insurance Number to use in verifying and reporting credit information to credit bureaus and credit collection agencies. If you wish to refuse consent of this right, then you must do so upon contracting with us. In doing so, you may not qualify for financial assistance through triOS.
Career Quiz
Take this quiz to learn more about where your interests can take you! The quiz gives you suggestions on what fields you may want to consider based on your responses. Give it a try!
Take The Quiz
